Let's take a look at the effect of the change.
If you want to change, you can find a reference picture that you want to change.
If you want to change today, the reference picture is like this.
Let's shrink it.
Let's start a change.
Before the change, we can harden the selection of these versions first.
Then make the example frame a little bigger.
In this way, the simulation will be faster.
Then we do this simulation.
Make it a little wider.
In this way, the simulation of the pants will be faster.
Then we use this editing tool.
We can select the line of the pants.
Because it is face-to-face, so we select the front and back pieces, each piece is fine.
Then press the SHIFT key, the level can be lowered.
At the same time, press the right key, you can pop out this animation frame.
Let's change it to 300 first.
Look at the effect of 300.
After the change, the back part is a bit behind the model.
Then we can use the grid tool to select the pants in the back.
Then we can select the pants in the back.
Select a little more.
Then select the green grid and pull it out.
Pull it out and then simulate.
You can simulate it quickly.
Then this length is still too short.
We have to continue to add length.
Let's add 200 first.
Look at the effect.
Then simulate.
Then 200, you can slightly simulate and adjust it.
Because there is a little bit of line in the model skin.
Then this length is not enough, we continue to add length.
Add to a length that suits you.
Here we are 30.
Then adjust it.
Then we add a little longer.
Then add 2 cm.
Then simulate again.
Then this length is almost the length I want.
Next, I will modify the shape of the pants.
First of all, I use this plus point division tool.
For example, I draw this point below.
Then add a point at a distance of 100 mm.
Wait a minute to shrink it a little bit inside.
Then the pants in the back are the same.
Then use the edit panel tool to select this point.
After selecting the point, we can press the left key to move.
Then at the same time as moving, we can click this shift key.
You can move the level to the right.
Then at the same time, click the right key again.
It will pop up this range of movement.
We enter 10 for the range of movement.
Just 1 cm.
Then the other side is also.
We select this point.
Then here we select the front point first.
Then press the shift key to move the level as before.
Then the range of movement is 10.
Then the back.
Then the range of movement is also 10 mm.
In this way, the pants will be a little smaller on both sides.
Then press the shift key to move the level.
Then we open this line.
What we are going to do next is that we can cut the pants into two sections.
Then we directly use the hook and loop tool to select this line.
Basic line.
Then press the right key to cut and trim.
Just cut it off, no need to trim.
Then we use the adjustment panel.
We use the adjustment panel tool to move this panel down a little bit.
Because we want to make the upper pants a little longer.
Then select these two pants.
Then find the external expansion of the panel.
Then expand it.
Let's take a look.
Here we can change the diameter to 25 mm.
Then we can choose the angle type here.
I choose extension here.
Then extend the inner line and hook it up.
The inner line is this line.
If you don't hook it up, this line will be gone.
After we add length, we can see that the panel here has become longer.
It is now overlapping with the bottom panel.
If you simulate it, it must be a little unstable.
So we use this adjustment tool to turn it over a little bit.
Then the top line can be adjusted.
And if it's connected, we just have to change one side.
Then we press the import button to choose these panels.
Then press Ctrl H for hardening.
Then do the sanding.
And then this paragraph.
Because there areRelay inside.
But if you can't see it, we will do the sanding directly.
It won't pull the chain.
And the back is the same.
And then there's this side.
And then the inside side.
I'll simulate it.
And then you can see a simulated effect.
And then what we're going to do next is to put the front of this pair of pants on the knee.
Add a vertical fold to make it a little brighter.
A more pronounced effect.
That's the same first of all.
We use the plus point division tool.
We can add this point above and below just now.
And then a distance of about 50.
And then confirm the following is the same.
Select the plus point division tool.
Select the top of the line.
Then press the right button.
You can pop up this dialogue frame.
And then we put the first paragraph into a 50.
And then confirm.
You can see that this point is added.
And then after we add it, we use this fold tool to make this order.
After we select the tool, we just click on it.
Click and then move the mouse to the other side.
You can press shift and then press the left button again.
You can draw this.
A line of this fold.
Then we can choose to extend this order above or below.
Then I choose below.
Then press the left button.
It will pop up a drawing of this fold.
Then you can choose a different type of fold here.
Then I choose to make an order here.
So choose the first default.
Then we change this width to 15 mm.
Then confirm.
Then I can see that one of its angles has been set.
That bright red.
It's 0 degrees.
The green is 360 degrees.
And then the next one is the same.
And then it goes down.
Then.
Width 15.
Then confirm.
That's it.
Then here you can see that it's half a piece longer.
Then open the simulation.
Then adjust it a little bit.
Then you can see that this paper is done.
Follow.
And now you can see this.
If it's a line, it's a line.
So it's an effect like this.
Then we're going to cut this.
This inner line is cut.
That's also a plus tool.
And then we're going to add a few points with the left button.
Then use the edit panel tool to frame these points.
Then right-click on the selected point.
Then we find the inner point of the division.
You can divide these points.
Then we click on the point.
It will show a choice of two lines.
Because there are two points overlapping here.
Then we choose which one.
Choose and then move.
Move.
You can come down a little bit.
Let's take a look at which line you chose.
Then I can see that I chose this line on the right.
Then I'll move a little bit to the right.
Then the following is the same.
Move the two points from the point.
Then we can frame the selection after moving them all away.
Move these choices a little bit to the side.
It doesn't have to be that long.
It's a little bit shorter.
Then simulation.
You can see that one of its effects will be a little bit better.
Then we go down this leg.
We can make it a little bit wider.
That's the same.
Use the edit panel tool to select this point.
Then after selection.
Then we press this left button to move.
Then press the shift key to level it.
That's it.
When moving, click the right button at the same time.
We can bounce out of this moving distance.
An input frame.
Here we have, for example, 15 mm.
Confirm.
Then the other two points are the same.
We choose this point.
We choose one side first.
Because these two sides are not on the same side.
Then it's also 15 mm.
Confirm.
Then the other side is also.
Select this.
Select it.
Then move 15 mm.
Confirm.
Then we can see the width of this pants.
Just change it.
Then we go to the bottom.
For example, below we want to change the effect of this belt draw.
First of all, we use the edit panel tool to select the belt top and bottom two panel lines.
Then right-click.
Our internal line diameter.
Then 10 mm.
Confirm.
Then after adding the internal line, you can colonize a panel.
Because it needs to have two layers.
It has the effect of this draw.
Then right-click, colonize the outer layer.
Then just put it down.
Then this panel is the same size.
Then we first want to remove it from the link.
If you don't remove it, you wait.
Wait a minute.
Change one.
A linked panel on top will be modified together.
Then after the removal.
Let's delete the line first.
Because it's a circle of powder.
If you don't change it, the simulation will be folded together later.
So delete this line first.
Then the inside line inside the line, then you don't have to delete it.
Then we manually make it powder.
The bottom and the bottom are covered.
Here is the type of powder line.
We are going to change it to powder.
Because it is from powder to powder together.
If you don't change it to powder, it will bulge.
Then the top and the top are the same.
Change to powder.
Then the side and the side.
You don't have to change this side.
Then we select the middle panel.
Double-click on the activation center point.
Then the activation center point.
We change one side.
The other side will be modified with this.
It's a little faster.
Then we move directly.
At the same time, we can click on the right.
It will pop up.
This is a simulation of the change.
Then you can enter this percentage.
For example, a size of 135.
Then confirm.
If you want it to be a little longer, you can modify it.
On this side.
There's a little bit behind.
It's an intersection.
It doesn't matter.
We right-click on the selected panel.
You can add it to the outside.
Then he can quickly arrange this panel for us.
Then we select this panel.
Make a modification of its material.
Because the short panel above.
It's a camera panel.
It's harder.
Then if you simulate it.
It doesn't have the effect of this draw.
So change to a louder, softer one.
The material.
Then simulate it.
Now there is no draw effect.
You don't have to care about it first.
Because it's now in the panel.
The particle range is relatively large.
So the draw effect is not good.
Wait for us to improve the quality.
It has a draw effect.
Then we'll go down.
And then the following words.
For example, we want a pocket on the side.
Add a pocket.
Then we first in the 2D window.
Enlarge the needed pocket.
Then we find this.
The inside of the diagonal tool.
Because we need to be in the panel.
Draw this.
A pocket of a technical inner line.
So you have to choose the inside of the diagonal.
Internal舉行
Then select.
Select the internal舉行 tool.
Then we can be in front.
Then it's very easy to use.
You can be in the panel.
That place.
The panel.
Press the left key to move.
You can draw a rectangular panel.
Then you want to draw a square.
Then you can press the shift key.
Then move the mouse to the left key.
You can draw a rectangular square.
Then in the panel.
The other place.
Press the left key.
Then it will pop up.
This is a drawing frame of the舉.
Here, for example, my pocket is.
A width of 180 mm.
Then the height is 220.
Then we click to confirm.
Then you draw an inner line of this pocket.
Then we remove the excess inner line.
Then we use the adjustment panel tool.
You can select this inner line.
After selecting, we can adjust.
Then we adjust the 2D window.
The 3D window will actually make a change.
Let's take a look at the effect after adjustment.
You can see it in the 3D window.
Then you can make a slight adjustment.
Then I think it's about the same.
Now we can see this pocket.
There is only one side.
There is no inner line on the other side.
Then let's see how to put it down.
The inner line is crossed to another panel.
Then we use the edit panel tool.
Double click this inner line.
Select the center.
Then right-click on the center line.
We can see that there is one.
Based on the line separation.
That's a new feature.
We choose it.
Based on the line separation.
In this way, you can see the 3D window.
Its inner line is crossed to another panel.
It's on a panel that's close to it.
You can see it.
Then we make a panel in the pocket.
That was the inner line.
Let's draw a panel in the pocket.
Then we directly select this one.
Shape tool.
Then in the 2D window.
Empty place.
Single click left.
Then pop up this one.
An input to make a shape.
Comparison frame.
That's what we just saw.
It's 180 mm wide.
And then the height is 220.
Then confirm it.
Then after drawing.
The following is to do the analysis.
You can see that it's not free.
Let's put it on.
Then we select the middle panel.
Then add it to the outside.
It can be simulated very quickly.
Then simulate.
Then this pocket is simulated.
You can see.
Now we can see this pocket.
It's going to be pasted.
So it's a relatively safe state.
Then we add a small panel on the side.
Make his pocket have a three-dimensional effect.
Then first use this edge panel tool.
Select this three-sided line.
Look at its length.
That's about 619.
A length.
Then you can remember.
Then we use the shape tool.
Then in the empty place.
Single click left.
Width 619.
About 119.
In terms of height.
For example, 35 mm.
This can also be modified.
Let's adjust the position.
Then use this sewing line.
For a sewing.
We first sewed on this inner line.
Then the sewing line just sewed.
Eliminate.
Then the other side.
And sew this pocket panel.
Then after sewing.
Let's pull it out a little bit first.
Then this side.
This small panel is selected.
Select and then right click.
We add to the side.
It's not necessary for us to arrange it manually.
He himself.
According to the relationship of the separation line.
Just quickly.
Modified.
Add over.
You can see.
Then we select it.
Then we select these two panels.
Please go to the right.
And then simulate.
You can see this pocket.
Becomes a three-dimensional effect.
There is a bit of a hole here.
Then we can select the separation line first.
Then modify a angle.
Because this side.
It needs to be more flat.
So the angle must be changed to a small angle of 180 degrees.
An angle.
For example, change to a 120, and then the simulation will become a little more even.
And then the simulation here is a little unstable.
Then we can use this.
Form tool
And then make an arrangement.
You can see the paper.
Arrangement is good.
Form setting is good.
Then the simulation can be seen.
It's more stable.
And then this pocket, if it's wider, the effect is not very good.
Then we can add an inner line to fold it in.
That is also to use this edit board tool to select the upper and lower two board lines.
Then right-click
We find the inner line between the lines.
In this case, it can add an inner line in the center.
And then just confirm it.
And then we're going to set the angle.
Before we set the angle, we switch the text to this text surface.
It can distinguish the front and the back of the text.
The bright one is the front.
The dark one is the back.
And then we're going to go in.
That's the other way around.
So it's 360 degrees.
Let's change it to 360.
And then we're going to simulate it.
You can see it's going in.
Fold it in.
And then after you fold it in, we're going to do it for better results.
We can fix a small section with a sewing line.
Use free sewing.
You can fix a small section.
How long?
You can do it yourself.
Uh, the effect is to do the sewing.
It's time for the sewing line.
And then there's a little stride here.
And then here's the type of sewing line.
It's going to change to a dot.
Because it's folded in half.
So it's a overlap.
And then simulate it.
Well, that way, it's going to be a little bit better.
Then we go down, and now the pocket, the pocket is flat, it's flat, so we want to make a pocket that has better effect, so we can make a shunzi or a gongzhi in the middle.
It's the same, select these two lines, we add an internal line in the middle, and then right-click to create an internal line between the lines.
Then confirm it, and then add this line to determine its center, and then add it from the center, and then the two sides will be even.
Then we use this folding tool again, and then select the internal line in the middle, and then to the left and right, you can just click on one side.
Then just in order, now we select the middle line.
Then we select the middle line, and then we select the internal line in the middle.
To switch, select this gongzhi.
Then we first change this width to 25, and then gongzhi.
Then the rest of the words do not need to directly click to confirm it.
Then we can see that this sheet is getting bigger.
Now let's take a look at this floating line.
The floating line is also sewed.
Then we reset the 3D arrangement position to make it flat first.
Because the board was a little deformed just now.
Make it flat first, and then adjust the position.
Then the words above, it is not sewed.
Then we want to make it a floating.
The floating is sewed at 0 degrees and 360 degrees on both sides.
Then this red line is the 0-degree line.
Then the floating line type has to be changed to a folding line.
Then the green line is a 360-degree line.
Then it is also a folding line on both sides.
Then we sew it up and change it.
In case we forget it later.
If you sew it up and change it once later, it's okay.
Then after that, we open the simulation.
Take a look at the good effect of the simulation.
Then you can see.
Then this formula is done.
Then this formula may not look good.
Let's see where there is a problem.
For example, change this 360-degree line to a smaller one.
Let it not look like it's folding.
Then it didn't improve.
Let's take a look again.
You can see that the line just now.
After the selection, there are two internal lines of a display.
That means there is an overlap of the internal line.
We can't overlap the internal line.
So we have to select it.
Select one of them and delete it.
There can only be one internal line.
Then this one should be a zero-degree line.
Re-automatically change it to a zero-degree line.
Then simulate it.
There is no effect.
That means there are other places that have not been changed.
Then we look down again.
Then here should be the problem of the floating line.
You can see that it is 180 degrees now.
We have to change it to 120 degrees.
A angle less than 180 degrees.
It will protrude out to both sides.
After that, its effect will be better.
You can see.
Then on these two sides.
We can also use free sewing.
Fix this seam.
If you want to sew a specific length of free sewing.
Then while you are sewing.
You can click on the right-click.
In this way, it can tell you the length of the floating line.
Enter the length you want.
Then you can see that it will follow the length you enter.
Do sewing.
Then the following is the same.
Right-click.
Then 20.
Confirm.
Then don't right-click on the other side.
Because free sewing has a blue dot.
It points you out to the end of a distance in the previous section.
You don't have to right-click again.
Then simulate.
Then this pocket.
A pocket made by the craftsman.
Then we are going to make a belt cover.
The belt cover.
We are in this pocket.
About one centimeter above.
For example, we just use that line to pin.
Then if you pin.
We can see.
The line that comes out of this pin.
It's down now.
So we're going to reverse it.
Put it on top.
Then this line.
Extended to the outside of the plate.
So it doesn't need to be extended.
Then we choose it.
Turn off the extension of the internal line.
It's not extended.
Then confirm.
The two internal lines are done.
Then this one.
The general pocket.
It may be a little longer.
Then we can choose this line.
Right-click.
Then we find this change.
Length.
Click to change the length.
Then you can see here.
It has a yellow arrow.
Now it's on the left.
On the right.
Then we have to extend to the left.
So you can switch its direction.
The end of the place.
Choose.
Its arrow is on the left.
Then now 97 degrees.
Then we add a little.
Add about 5 mm.
It's about 102.
You can see it's getting a little longer.
Then confirm.
Then the other side is also selected.
Right-click.
Change the length.
Then this arrow on the right is correct.
Then the length is also slightly longer.
About 5 mm.
About 82.
Confirm.
Then we press the Shift key to select two lines.
You can see that its length is 184.
Then we can use the lift tool.
We select this lift tool.
Then click on the blank place.
Then 184.
Then the height is about 75.
Then confirm.
Then the cover plate is processed.
Then put it on.
Also use the free smear.
Then after sewing.
I also choose the same.
Add it to the outside.
You don't have to arrange it manually.
He will run over and arrange it with him.
Then adjust it.
Open the simulation.
Then this cover pocket is made.
Then the other side.
No need to draw again.
We directly select these panels.
Ctrl D.
Then copy the face of the panel.
Then adjust the position.
Hardening.
Ctrl H hardening.
Modify.
Then this side.
The pocket is also a bit.
This simulation is not stable.
So we use the lift tool to set it.
Then the other extra line.
Delete this line of the layer.
No need.
Then this is also deleted.
Only these two are left.
Then simulate.
Then you can see the simulation is stable.
Then we put it.
Then we cancel the hardening.
Right click.
Cancel hardening.
Then simulate.
Then let's take a look at the following.
Next to do.
For example, we do this.
The front of this T side.
First we select this line.
You can see it has angles.
So we have to modify its angle.
Because this side doesn't need angles.
180 degrees.
Then select.
Use the lift tool.
Select a closed pattern.
Select all four sides.
Press the Shift key to select more.
Then select one side.
Then right click.
Lift as a plate.
Then delete the rest of the lines.
Then the back is the same.
Select all four sides.
Then on the selected edge.
Right click.
Can enlarge a little.
Then we select the first one.
Connect as a plate.
Then you can put it down.
Then delete the rest of the lines.
Select it.
Delete.
Then sew it.
You can do the smoothing below.
Then sew below and below.
After sewing below.
The line type has to be changed to fold.
Because the top.
It is the inner line.
The inner line and the outside line.
The default is the fold.
So you don't have to manually change it.
There are two outside lines below.
We have to change it to fold.
Then the back is the same.
The top and the top inner line.
The bottom and the bottom fold.
Change to fold.
Then.
On the other side.
We can directly select the plate.
Press D.
Then press the contact plate.
Then adjust the position.
Then use this line.
The side of this sticker is sewed.
Then the inside is also sewed.
Then after sewing.
We use this.
Select the moving tool.
Select these four stickers.
Then you can choose in 2D.
You can choose in the 3D window.
Then on the selection panel.
Right click.
Add to the inside.
Then add to the inside.
Model.
After the simulation.
It's a little unstable here.
That's because when we add.
There are three layers here.
It may be recharged in one piece.
So it's a little unstable.
Then we have to make a adjustment.
That's also.
We use the tool.
That's the tool.
That's the plate we point at first.
Point at the front of this plate at the back.
So it's the front of the top.
Point to this sticker.
Explain this.
The top plate.
Outside of this sticker.
Then the back is the same.
Click on this first.
Then click on this side.
That means this cool piece.
Outside of the side.
After the simulation.
The effect is not very good.
Because it has three layers here.
So the next one has to point down.
Then the side points to this cool piece.
Because the side is in the middle.
Then simulate.
You can see.
Now it's three layers.
That is.
There is a correct order.
So it's more stable.
Then below.
We see this cool corner.
Then the cool corner.
There is no side.
So we are the same.
We choose it.
Right click.
Then.
The inner line is tight.
Then here.
We are also about 25.
Then turn it in the opposite direction.
Let it be inside the board.
Then click to confirm.
That's it.
Then the inner line is good.
The board is not yet.
The board is also.
Use this hook.
Expansion tool.
Then select the four sides.
A pattern of closure.
Then on the selected line.
Right click hook as a board.
Then put it down.
Put it down.
Then the front.
It's the same.
Four sides selected.
Then hook it as a board.
Then put it down.
Right click.
Then use this line.
Funnel.
Then the following tunnel line type.
To be changed to the top.
Then the back.
Then also changed to top.
Then the other side.
We select the two three sides.
Control plus D.
And then the other side.
Include a permanently located board.
And then put this to the back.
Put it in the appropriate position of the back piece
Turn it over
Then use the line tool to divide the side
Do this analysis
Then the analysis is also the same
We adjust the board tool
Select these four boards
On the selected board, right click on the 3D window
Right click
Add to this inside
Then you can see that it is quickly arranged to this inside
Then simulate it is stable
Then let's take a look at some details
May need to adjust
For example, this cover
First of all
Generally, it has about two layers
Then we can add this inside line first
We select these three sides
Then the inside line diameter
Then the diameter is about one centimeter
Then click to confirm
Then use the adjustment board tool
Select the right button on the board
Then there is a cone layer here
Outside
We are outside
Then let's make a cone
One cover
Put it down
And simulate
Because the particle diameter is now relatively large
We can choose it first
Not it slightly reduce
For example, 12
Then the simulated result
Will be a little better
More subtle
Then the other side is the same, select the cover and right-click on the outer part of the colon layer, and then simulate it again.
Then the cover is processed, then we add a fabric.
After adding the fabric, we will deal with this detail again, because there is a production effect of butterfly knot and pig nose buckle.
Then we click on this tool to improve the quality, and then we generally do not select the first three, the simulation quality does not need to be selected.
Then click to confirm, and then let it simulate for a while.
Then after the simulation is done, then we can pause the simulation first, and then deal with other details.
Then here, for example, we do a butterfly knot, side to side butterfly knot effect.
Let's turn off this basic display first.
Then we first determine the position of this plus butterfly knot.
Then we switch to this position first.
Then we select this random color, because the fabric was a bit too dark just now.
Let's adjust a brighter random color.
Then select the 3D window and click on two panels.
You need to add this position of the butterfly knot to determine first.
After determining, then we can use this inner circle to draw two of this.
Then the next hole.
We draw a ellipse.
Then on the other side, we can select it, ctrl c, ctrl v, copy and paste.
Then put it on the other side.
The size of this circle can be adjusted, and the position can be adjusted.
You can make it bigger or smaller.
Smaller can be enlarged.
Then move.
Move and rotate can be modified.
Then we adjust to a suitable position.
Then we use the edit panel tool.
We press the shift key to select two panels.
Right click.
Then we find that there is a shortcut loop.
Rotate.
Then there are two holes.
And then we draw a butterfly knot small panel.
Draw a smaller panel.
Then we find this panel has a quick arrangement of this small icon.
There is a small icon with a low position at the upper right corner of the panel.
Click it can be quickly arranged.
Then adjust its position.
This version is a bit too long, so we can shrink it a little bit.
Since other versions don't need to be simulated, we can freeze it.
Then we select it, double click on the activation center point.
Then we can shrink the proportion.
Then a little bit smaller.
Then adjust the position.
Then we click on the version inside the hole to see where it is.
Then at the bottom, we need to add an internal line.
For the internal line, we can manually add one.
After adding it, we can simulate it.
Use free simulation to simulate a small section.
Then the other side is also a small section.
Then this internal line, the position can also be moved.
For example, we move to this hole.
Move a little bit outside.
Then the outside is the same.
At the hole, you can see this internal line.
Move a little bit.
Then we can untangle the inside first.
Then it's almost done.
Before we simulate, we can first reduce the example example.
Because it's a relatively small version.
If it's 20, the simulation may not be stable.
So let's reduce it first.
You can adjust it to below 5.
Then you can simulate it after adjustment.
Then you can simulate it.
Simulate.
Let's adjust the details a little bit.
Adjust it a little bit over there.
Then simulate.
Then we can freeze it.
Because it doesn't need to be simulated.
Freeze it.
Then the following is a method of making a butterfly's ear.
Then freeze this eye.
Then the ear is also used as a lifting tool.
Just draw another board.
Because its width can be adjusted.
We can draw another one.
Then we can adjust it.
We can adjust it.
Then use the adjustment board tool to choose the board.
Quickly arrange to this butterfly's ear.
Then adjust the position of this board a little bit.
Because the butterfly's ear, we are doing a fake effect.
Not a real butterfly's ear.
Make a fake one.
So I'm doing one side first.
Then do the other side.
Then a little bit longer.
After that, we first determine the position.
Draw a few inner lines.
Because the butterfly has ears.
So we have to draw an inner line first.
Then we have to draw two in total.
Then here is almost the center of the position.
Add one more.
Double-click to end.
Then use this adjustment tool.
Then we are on the inner line.
Select it.
There will be such a small icon.
Then fold it over.
Then the other one is also folded back.
In this way, the effect of the ear of the butterfly's ear is already there.
A Z-shaped effect.
Then we select it.
Then it's the same.
We have to change the position of the center of gravity first.
If it is 20, it may not be stable.
Then.
Then if the conflict.
We also slightly change a little bit.
Then slightly adjust the position.
Then we slightly add two pins.
Press the W key to click on the board.
You can add pins.
Then.
Then this board.
We add one on each side.
Select two lines.
Add one in the middle.
No line.
Because we're going to put the butterfly's ear on it later.
Okay.
Confirm it.
Then we use this line.
We can directly in the 3D window.
Do the smoothing.
Then smoothing it.
Then open the simulation.
Look at it first.
It's a good simulation effect.
Then the simulation here is.
Stable.
Then we're going to do the other side.
The other side is simpler.
We choose it.
Control C.
Control V.
Just stick it out.
Put it down.
Then slightly adjust this position.
He put it over.
Slightly adjust.
Then.
Adjusting the first.
A little closer.
If it's too far.
He might fly over to simulate.
It might cause him to stuck.
So, if it's a little more.
As close as you can.
And then.
Far it up at this router.
I don't want it to be crossed.
If it's too far.
Then after dyeing.
You can simulate it.
Let me just put it there.
That's okay.
I'll leave to this.
The simulation here is also stable, no need to change
This line is no longer needed
Make it smoother, select these two lines first
Then delete
Then we draw a small board
It is a small board that will be folded in the middle of the butterfly knot
In this case, the effect is not good, we add another small board
Then sew it up
Then sew to the middle of the two sides, a little bit average
It's okay
Let it cover and block the two sides of this ear
Then choose its quick arrangement
Put it near it, then make a slight adjustment
Then adjust its position
Then it's the same, you can adjust the diameter a little bit
Because this board is very small, you can adjust it to 1
Then simulate
Then add a fixing pin here
To prevent it from absorbing the simulation, let it stretch
Just this fixing pin, pull this board out
Don't suck into this board inside
Then let it simulate and stabilize first
Then we hold down the W key and click on the fixing pin
You can delete other fixing pins
Then simulate
Let its butterfly knot naturally drop down
Then a little bit more
Then wait a little bit
Let it slowly drop down
Then I will pause here
Almost a position
Let it pause
Then it is such an effect
If you think it's not good, you can simulate it again
Let it drop down again
That's good
This butterfly knot, we can choose it
Then freeze
Freeze
Don't let it simulate
Let it freeze
Then we do this next
The effect of this eye is a draw
Then there is the effect of the eye and the nose of the pig
Then also determine the position first
Use the inner circle
Then in the board
Press the Shift key to draw a positive circle
Press the Shift key and then move
You can draw a positive circle
Then this circle size is drawn
If you think it's big or small, it can be modified
Then we can adjust its position a little bit
Then the size of the fire center point
Then the ratio is reduced
Then copy
Ctrl C
Ctrl V
Copy and paste one
Put it on the other side
Then adjust the position a little bit
If you think it's appropriate
Let's choose these two circles below
Use the edit board tool to choose two circles
Press the Shift key to choose two circles
Then we find this cut and paste
Because we can't delete this circle
We have to keep this circle
Because I'm going to add this object to the circle later
Let's move this board out first
Then we first turn it on
Turn off the fire first
Then turn it back on
Because later
If you draw a rope, you have to go through this hole
If you don't turn it back on
This board is not easy to simulate
So turn it back on and hide it
Hide it
Then you can see there is a hole
Then we draw a rectangular small board
A small board of rope
We can draw a little bigger first
Because this can be adjusted
Then we add an inner line in the middle
Because we are going to do a fold later
After adding, we find this board
Then move it to this area first
Then
Adjust the position a little
Then use this vertical arrangement
Select the middle line
Make a fold on both sides
Fold over
Then choose the move tool
Then select the move this board
Move it to this area
A little closer
Is the simulation
Will be faster and more stable
So let's move it a little closer
Then the position is almost
Then we use the fake sewing tool
Fake sewing is that we use the sewing line
Sewing tools or fake sewing tools
Can fix this line to this
On the board of this pants
Then I choose the fake sewing here
That's also very simple
Select the board
Click on the board again
You can add two parts to fix
Then we fix one in the middle
To prevent it from opening more
Because we are going to add this gas later
Then this
The line length of the fake sewing can be changed
For example, change to 4 mm first
Then and its position
The tool can move the position of the fake sewing
Then before the simulation
We also change the particle diameter of the board
5 below
Then the gap is also slightly reduced
Because the particle diameter is large
The simulation will shake and not be stable
So for this small board
Be sure to reduce the particle diameter
Then simulate it
Then we can save it
Then after the simulation
This is our model
Then the line of thison the side
This is a gap
Then we can clear the gap
Then we can remove the game
Then we can delete it
Then we can trace the lines
Then the second thing
Then here we have a base line
We don't need it anymore
Because it has angles
If it is not deleted
It's flat
Delete it
So it turns rounder
Then simulate
After deleting this inner line, it will become a little smoother on this side.
Then we add an eye.
After adding the eye, we will fine-tune this detail.
Then add this value type, we choose to add.
Then confirm.
Then there is glue here.
We click on the glue to stick it over.
Then adjust it a little bit, put it near it.
Then this line is a bit too short, we choose to change it a little bit longer.
For example, this gas line is too short.
Then we increase it a little bit, and then simulate it.
Then the simulation can be seen that it will be a little deformed.
Then we pause the simulation and cancel it back.
This is because the component has a weight.
Then we find this butterfly knot little icon in the object window.
Then we find a data map of ZubyCode.
Click.
Then in the understand counter below.
We found this amount.
It is almost 10.2 cm30 expenditures.
It's too heavy, that's why this volumetric square is too small.
like 10assembles and jie full, with such a weight
Therefore, we need to reduce the amount of the component a little bit.
For example, 0.01 made it to be light.
Then we simulate it again, you can see that it will not fall down, it will be better to be floating in the air, and then we will adjust the position of this Zubicode first, and then adjust it.
If you want to adjust it, it may take a little time, if you want to make it look good, you can adjust it a little bit.
Then rotate it a little bit here.
Then after almost, we choose the plate, and then add a little bit of the thickness of it.
For example, add to 2, make it a little thicker.
Then we simulate it a little bit, because this Zubicode may not look good, because it is relatively flat.
Then we simulate it now, let it slowly fall down.
Let it be a little more natural, because it is relatively flat now, and the effect is not good.
Then I here, this Zubicode plate may be drawn a little longer.
Then if you are drawing it yourself, you can make it a little shorter.
It doesn't have to be very long.
I'm a little long here.
Then now simulate it a little bit, let it fall down.
Okay, then adjust this component a little bit.
Then it's almost there.
Let's freeze it.
Then we're going to do this.
Let's shift W to display this hidden plate just now.
Then use the button tool.
We add this button on this next plate.
Then the other side is the same.
Click to add this button.
Then the button is good, we can select the button.
Then we go to the button to change its shape.
Because now it's a button with four holes.
We go to the button.
The ice-cream machine shape is found at 7 o'clock.
There are three here.
We choose one in the middle.
Then it has such an effect.
Then we can change the size.
Then it's too small to make me a little bigger.
Then now.
The button.
It's not on this plate.
It's not in this plate.
Then we can use this.
Select and move the button tool.
Then select all the buttons.
Then there is a length of the line here.
Whether it is zero.
Then we can change a negative number.
For example, the negative three can be seen.
He ran to the inside of this plate himself.
Then we can change its type of metal.
Then it's almost done.
Then adjust it a little bit.
A little bit below me.
Because this is a little too long.
It floats on top.
Maybe the effect is not good.
Then now what we do is all on one side.
On the other side, it's easier.
We choose these butterfly-shaped panels.
Then press D.
Cron.
Cron comes out of a joint panel.
You don't have to re-model it twice.
You can just press D.
Then you can see it.
Cron came out.
Then.
Then the seven eyes are the same.
Press D.
Then put it on the other side.
In this way, our pants.
This change is done.
Then switch this to the surface of the dense texture.
Then we can activate its clothes.
Then turn off all these line displays.
Then our clothes also use this fabric.
This is wrong.
Use a black fabric.
Then the outer clothes panel is also selected.
Then also use a yellow.
Yellowish color of this fabric.
Then the pants.
Freeze.
Simulate this top.
Then we can change a move after simulation.
Then we choose a relatively simple one here.
An action of putting down the arm.
Then wait a moment.
Let him put down his hand first.
And then.
Is this this?
You can see.
Is this all?
It's this.
See.
Then, after all that, we'll freeze it all.
All frozen.
After the freeze.
Then you can see.
This is one of the effects.
Then we change this pair of pants to this side and we're done